rardownloads.com 2012-11-01

# Untitled Page

**Privacy Policy**

Privacy Policy

[RARDownloads.com](http://www.rardownloads.com/) values your privacy. In a nutshell, this Privacy Policy is to ensure you that we will never sell, rent, trade, or abuse your information.

For more specific concerns, please take the time to read the rest of the Privacy Policy below.

**What information do we collect from you?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

When purchasing a product, you will be required to enter your credit card number, billing address, and other relevant information. However, online transactions are performed over an SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) server. This means that you're information is safe as it travels online. Following the transaction, our system will automatically delete all your credit card information except the last four digits, which are retained only for reference purposes.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  

  * To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  

  * To help you find a more suitable lender you can borrow hard money from. RARDownloads.com is designed to help you connect with the lender closest to your location to make it easier for you to get financed.  

  * To determine where to send newsletters and email alerts from RARDownloads.com. Once you subscribe to out official newsletter, you will receive emails from us that can help you in your real estate business and overall financial health. This information may also be sent to you via phone calls.  

  * To determine where to send promos and product launches. RARDownloads.com holds promotions and in some cases offers discounts to its subscribers. Information regarding these exclusive, subscriber- only promos and discounts are sent through phone or email.  

**Do We Use Cookies?**   
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us with your last visit to our site preferences in order for us to improve our site upon your next visit. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers, including Google to assist us in better understanding our site visitors, for instance show you ads on sites on the internet based on your preference during your prior visit on our site. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.    

**Unsubscribe/Opt-out**   
In any case you no longer want to receive any form of communication from us, you can unsubscribe or opt-out from the system through any of these easy ways:

  * You may opt-out from receiving our emails by following the instructions on any commercial email you receive from us. Usually found at the bottom part of emails you receive from us.  

  * Tell us through email: [support@ RARDownloads.com](mailto:support@rardownloads). Simply put “Attn: Newsletter Unsubscribe” on the subject line of the email to opt out.  

  * You may also opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads)<http://www.google.com/privacy/ads>. Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). It does mean that the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns.  

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

One of the methods we use is the SSL or Secure Sockets Layer to make sure your personal and credit card information is safe online.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Affiliated sites, linked sites, and advertisements**  
[RARDownloads.com](http://www.rardownloads/) expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a [ RARDownloads.com](http://www.rardownloads/) page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through RARDownloads.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. ocalHardMoney.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. [ RARDownloads.com](http://www.rardownloads/) does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of RARDownloads.com and this policy.

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.RARDownloads.com](http://www.foreclosure1st.com/)

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. It is understood that you have read, and agreed to, the Privacy Policy before entering your information.

**Children**  
[ RARDownloads.com](http://www.rardownloads/) does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 18 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 18 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe RARDownloads.com has any information from or about anyone under 18, please contact us at the address listed below.

Contacting Us  
We can be reached by contacting:  
Email: [privacy@RARDownloads.com](mailto:privacy@rardownloads)  
Main Office: Web Networks, Inc  
PO Box 10301  
Tampa , Fl. 33679

**Changes to this Policy**  
[ RARDownloads.com](http://www.rardownloads/) reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**GOVERNING LAW**  
THIS POLICY AND THE USE OF THIS SITE ARE GOVERNED BY FLORIDA LAW. IF A DISPUTE ARISES UNDER THIS POLICY WE AGREE TO FIRST TRY TO RESOLVE IT WITH THE HELP OF A MUTUALLY AGREED-UPON MEDIATOR IN THE FOLLOWING LOCATION: HILLSBOROUGH COUNTY. ANY COSTS AND FEES OTHER THAN ATTORNEY FEES ASSOCIATED WITH THE MEDIATION WILL BE SHARED EQUALLY BY EACH OF US. IF IT PROVES IMPOSSIBLE TO ARRIVE AT A MUTUALLY SATISFACTORY SOLUTION THROUGH MEDIATION, WE AGREE TO SUBMIT THE DISPUTE TO BINDING ARBITRATION AT THE FOLLOWING LOCATION: HILLSBOROUGH COUNTY, UNDER THE RULES OF THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION.

JUDGMENT UPON THE AWARD RENDERED BY THE ARBITRATION MAY BE ENTERED IN ANY COURT WITH JURISDICTION TO DO SO. REIWIRED.COM IS CONTROLLED, OPERATED AND ADMINISTERED ENTIRELY WITHIN FLORIDA. THIS STATEMENT AND THE POLICIES OUTLINED HEREIN ARE NOT INTENDED TO AND

DO NOT CREATE ANY CONTRACTUAL OR OTHER LEGAL RIGHTS IN OR ON BEHALF OF ANY PARTY.
